export const sports = [
    {
        question: 'What sport practice Cristiano Ronaldo is known for?',
        answers: [
            'Soccer',
            'Tennis',
            'Golf',
            'Basketball'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Soccer'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many referees have a soccer game?',
        answers: [
            '6',
            '1',
            '4',
            '5'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '4'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who has been the Formula 1 Driver with the most victories in the history of the sport?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Nico Rosberg',
            'Juan Pablo Montoya'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Lewis Hamilton'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the most popular sport in the India?',
        answers: [
            'Football',
            'Hockey',
            'Cricket',
            'Tennis'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Cricket'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the ball in the world cup in 1978?',
        answers: [
            'Adidas Pro',
            'Nike Fusion',
            'Adidas Tango',
            'Puma Air Max'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Adidas Tango'
    }
]

export const programming = [
    {
        question: 'What is the meaning of HTML?',
        answers: [
            'Hipo Type Mongo Language',
            'High Time Marking Letters',
            'Hello To Modern Language',
            'Hyper Text Markup Language'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Hyper Text Markup Language'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the meaning of MEAN?',
        answers: [
            'Mango Express Angulo Node',
            'Mongo Express Angular Node',
            'Main Enforced Appetizer Node',
            'Mean is the name of the programming language'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Mongo Express Angular Node'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which one of the following is not a library of JavaScript?',
        answers: [
            'jQuery',
            'Django',
            'Anime.js',
            'Hammer.js'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Django'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the function of git switch?',
        answers: [
            'Switch branches',
            'Switch to a new project',
            'The same as git log',
            'Switch into the git pull'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Switch branches'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the creator of the programming language Java?',
        answers: [
            'Dennis Ritchie',
            'James Gosling',
            'Ada Lovelace',
            'Guido van Rossum'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'James Gosling'
    }
]

export const science = [
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the planet that is the closest to the sun?',
        answers: [
            'Venus',
            'Earth',
            'Mercury',
            'Mars'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Mercury'
    },
    {
        question: 'The chromosomes are made of what?',
        answers: [
            'RNA',
            'DNA',
            'Protein',
            'Carbon'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'DNA'
    },
    {
        question: 'How is the name of the particles subatomic with negative charge?',
        answers: [
            'Proton',
            'Neutron',
            'Positron',
            'Electron'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Electron'
    },
    {
        question: 'Why the Sun shines?',
        answers: [
            'Because it is hot',
            'Because of the nuclear fusion process',
            'Because it is bright',
            'Because it is a atom'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Because of the nuclear fusion process'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the age of the universe?',
        answers: [
            '13.8 billion years',
            '13.7 billion years',
            '15 billion years',
            '14.1 billion years'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '13.8 billion years'
    }
]

export const history = [
    {
        question: 'Who was the first president of the United States?',
        answers: [
            'Thomas Jefferson',
            'Abraham Lincoln',
            'George Washington',
            'John Adams'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'George Washington'
    },
    {
        question: 'What was the nationality of Ernesto Che Guevara?',
        answers: [
            'Argentinian',
            'Cuban',
            'Mexican',
            'Uruguayan'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Argentinian'
    },
    {
        question: 'What volcano devastated Pompeii?',
        answers: [
            'Mount Etna',
            'Mount Vesuvius',   
            'Mount St. Helens',
            'Mount Everest'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Mount Vesuvius'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who said the earth revolves around the sun?',
        answers: [
            'Nicolaus Copernicus',
            'Galileo Galilei',
            'Arisarch of samus',
            'All of the above'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which year is the first spain constitution, la Pepa?',
        answers: [
            '1821',
            '1812',
            '1722',
            '1902'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '1812'

    }
]

export const geography = [
    {
        question: 'What is the capital of Spain?',
        answers: [
            'Madrid',
            'Barcelona',
            'Valencia',
            'Seville'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Madrid'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many continents are there in the world?',
        answers: [
            '7',
            '8',
            '4',
            '5'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '7'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the higher lake in the world?',
        answers: [
            'Lake Superior',
            'Lake Michigan',
            'Pacific Ocean',
            'Caspian Sea'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Caspian Sea'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many countries are in Africa?',
        answers: [
            '54',
            '71',
            '60',
            '37'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '54'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which one of this rivers is not the most important in Asia?',
        answers: [
            'Yangtze',
            'Sosuang',
            'Tigris',
            'Lena'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Sosuang'
    }
]